Guide to the Robert F. Harding, collector, railroad photographs, [ca. 1890-1959]
Harding, Robert F. (collector) railroad photographs, [ca. 1890-1959]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert F. Harding, collector, railroad photographs, [ca. 1890-1959]
2019
Robert F. Harding.
20 items.
Photographs and newsclippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Subjects include crewmen, locomotives, other rolling stock, freight yards, a wreck, right-of-way, and other views, chiefly of the New York, Ontario, and Western Railway. Also, two clippings pertaining to Marblehead, Massachusetts railroads.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subjects include crewmen, locomotives, other rolling stock, freight yards, a wreck, right-of-way, and other views, chiefly of the New York, Ontario, and Western Railway. Also, two clippings pertaining to Marblehead, Massachusetts railroads.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Harding, Robert F.; New York, Ontario, and Western Railway Co.
Subjects:
Railroad accidents.; Railroads--Massachusetts--Marblehead.; Railroads--New York.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- N.Y.O. - H.R. [Hudson River?] Railroad. White Car Mail Train, 1890. (Box 1)
- Engine named "Pharsalia." Built by Baldwin in 1872. Sold in 1872. Was placed in class "F" (maybe for funny looking??). (Box 1)
- Engine No. 61 with six men in front. Northern Division. Copied from a print Harold Walker had in 1948. Undated, but early. (Box 1)
- Freight yard, Weehawken, New Jersey. Oct. 2, 1959. (Box 1)
- New York, Ontario and Western coal docks, no rails, Weehawken, New Jersey, Oct. 2, 1959. (Box 1)
- Engine No. 44 with two railroad men in front. Undated, but early. (Box 1)
- Train with Engine No. 140 at Haver? Railroad Station. Undated. (Box 1)
- M. & U.R.R. Co. Engine No. 6. Undated. (Box 1)
- Large field with railroad tracks running through it. Wooden post with N.Y. 324 on it, in center of field. Undated. (Box 1)
- N.Y.O. & W. Engine No. 53 with coal car behind. Undated. (Box 1)
- N.Y.O. & W. Engine No. 54 with coal car. Another engine behind. Undated. (Box 1)
- N.Y.O. & W. Train wreck. Train with Engine No. 275 hit another train head on. Undated. (Box 1)
- N.Y.O. & W. Caboose No. 8128 with six railroad men in front. Undated. (Box 1)
- N.Y.O. & W. Engine No. 81 and coal car in freight yard. Undated. (Box 1)
- Railroad bridge going over a dirt road near white frame house. Undated. (Box 1)
- N.Y.O. & W. Caboose No. 8105 with five men in front. From left to right, Dell Allen, engineer Kenny, flagman "Kodak" Thompson, unknown, and fireman Jude Cooper. Oneida. Undated. (Box 1)
- Bell with wooden post nearby with N.Y. 324 on it. Undated. (Box 1)
- N.Y.O. & W. train with Engine No. 68 with two railroad men in front. Undated. (Box 1)
- Engine with "Pittston" and L.V.R. on the front. Undated. (Box 1)
- Engine with four men in front and one in the engine. Undated. (Box 1)